Guide to the Samir Farid Collection AD.MC.011
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Appointment with the Lover, موعد مع الحبيب, 5211; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 15, موعد مع الحبيب, 5226; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 16, موعد مع الحبيب, 5227; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 17, موعد مع الحبيب, 5228; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 18, موعد مع الحبيب, 5229; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 19, موعد مع الحبيب, 5230; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 20, موعد مع الحبيب, 5231; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 21, موعد مع الحبيب, 5232; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 22, موعد مع الحبيب, 5233; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 23, موعد مع الحبيب, 5234; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 24, موعد مع الحبيب, 5235; Rafla, Helmy
  - Appointment with the Lover Still 25, موعد مع الحبيب, 5236; Rafla, Helmy
- When We Love, عندما نحب, 5287; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 1, عندما نحب, 5288; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 2, عندما نحب, 5289; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 3, عندما نحب, 5290; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 4, عندما نحب, 5291; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 5, عندما نحب, 5292; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 6, عندما نحب, 5293; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 7, عندما نحب, 5294; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 8, عندما نحب, 5295; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 9, عندما نحب, 5296; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 10, عندما نحب, 5297; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 11, عندما نحب, 5298; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 12, عندما نحب, 5299; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 13, عندما نحب, 5300; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 14, عندما نحب, 5301; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 15, عندما نحب, 5302; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 16, عندما نحب, 5303; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 17, عندما نحب, 5304; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 18, عندما نحب, 5305; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - When We Love Still 19, عندما نحب, 5306; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
- The Olive Branch, غصن الزيتون, 5307; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 1, غصن الزيتون, 5308; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 2, غصن الزيتون, 5309; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 3, غصن الزيتون, 5310; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 4, غصن الزيتون, 5311; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 5, غصن الزيتون, 5312; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 6, غصن الزيتون, 5313; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 7, غصن الزيتون, 5314; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 8, غصن الزيتون, 5315; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 9, غصن الزيتون, 5316; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 10, غصن الزيتون, 5317; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 11, غصن الزيتون, 5318; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 12, غصن الزيتون, 5319; Bedeer, Sayed
  - The Olive Branch Still 13, غصن الزيتون, 5320; Bedeer, Sayed
- The Lover, العاشقه, 5321; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 1, العاشقه, 5322; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 2, العاشقه, 5323; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 3, العاشقه, 5324; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 4, العاشقه, 5325; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 5, العاشقه, 5326; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 6, العاشقه, 5327; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 7, العاشقه, 5328; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 8, العاشقه, 5329; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 9, العاشقه, 5330; Ziyada, Sayed
  - The Lover Still 10, العاشقه, 5331; Ziyada, Sayed
- According to Your Taste, على كيفك, 5332; Rafla, Helmy
  - According to Your Taste Still 1, على كيفك, 5333; Rafla, Helmy
  - According to Your Taste Still 2, على كيفك, 5334; Rafla, Helmy
  - According to Your Taste Still 3, على كيفك, 5335; Rafla, Helmy
  - According to Your Taste Still 4, على كيفك, 5336; Rafla, Helmy
  - According to Your Taste Still 5, على كيفك, 5337; Rafla, Helmy
  - According to Your Taste Still 6, على كيفك, 5338; Rafla, Helmy
  - According to Your Taste Still 7, على كيفك, 5339; Rafla, Helmy
- Women's Enemy, عرو المرأه, 5340; Abdel Fattah Hassan
  - Women's Enemy Still 1, عرو المرأه, 5341; Abdel Fattah Hassan
  - Women's Enemy Still 2, عرو المرأه, 5342; Abdel Fattah Hassan
  - Women's Enemy Still 3, عرو المرأه, 5343; Abdel Fattah Hassan
  - Women's Enemy Still 4, عرو المرأه, 5344; Abdel Fattah Hassan
  - Women's Enemy Still 5, عرو المرأه, 5345; Abdel Fattah Hassan
  - Women's Enemy Still 6, عرو المرأه, 5346; Abdel Fattah Hassan
  - Women's Enemy Still 7, عرو المرأه, 5347; Abdel Fattah Hassan
- The Smiles of Fate, ضحكات القدر, 5348; Hassan, Ilhamy
  - The Smiles of Fate Still 1, ضحكات القدر, 5349; Hassan, Ilhamy
  - The Smiles of Fate Still 2, ضحكات القدر, 5350; Hassan, Ilhamy
  - The Smiles of Fate Still 3, ضحكات القدر, 5351; Hassan, Ilhamy
  - The Smiles of Fate Still 4, ضحكات القدر, 5352; Hassan, Ilhamy
  - The Smiles of Fate Still 5, ضحكات القدر, 5353; Hassan, Ilhamy
- The Miracle, المعجزه, 5354
  - The Miracle Still 1, المعجزه, 5355
  - The Miracle Still 2, المعجزه, 5356
  - The Miracle Still 3, المعجزه, 5357
  - The Miracle Still 4, المعجزه, 5358
  - The Miracle Still 5, المعجزه, 5359
  - The Miracle Still 6, المعجزه, 5360
  - The Miracle Still 7, المعجزه, 5361
  - The Miracle Still 8, المعجزه, 5362
  - The Miracle Still 9, المعجزه, 5363
  - The Miracle Still 10, المعجزه, 5364
  - The Miracle Still 11, المعجزه, 5365
  - The Miracle Still 12, المعجزه, 5366
- The Genius and Love, العبقريه و الحب, 5367; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 1, العبقريه و الحب, 5368; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 2, العبقريه و الحب, 5369; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 3, العبقريه و الحب, 5370; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 4, العبقريه و الحب, 5371; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 5, العبقريه و الحب, 5372; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 6, العبقريه و الحب, 5373; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 7, العبقريه و الحب, 5374; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 8, العبقريه و الحب, 5375; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 9, العبقريه و الحب, 5376; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 10, العبقريه و الحب, 5377; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 11, العبقريه و الحب, 5378; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 12, العبقريه و الحب, 5379; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 13, العبقريه و الحب, 5380; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 14, العبقريه و الحب, 5381; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 15, العبقريه و الحب, 5382; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 16, العبقريه و الحب, 5383
  - The Genius and Love Still 17, العبقريه و الحب, 5384; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 18, العبقريه و الحب, 5385; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 19, العبقريه و الحب, 5386; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 20, العبقريه و الحب, 5387; Ahmed al Sab'awi
  - The Genius and Love Still 21, العبقريه و الحب, 5388; Ahmed al Sab'awi
- The Fatwa, الفتوه, 5478; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 1, الفتوه, 5479; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 2, الفتوه, 5480; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 3, الفتوه, 5481; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 4, الفتوه, 5482; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 5, الفتوه, 5483; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 6, الفتوه, 5484; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 7, الفتوه, 5485; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 8, الفتوه, 5486; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 9, الفتوه, 5487; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 10, الفتوه, 5488; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 11, الفتوه, 5489; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 12, الفتوه, 5490; Abu Seif, Salah
  - The Fatwa Still 13, الفتوه, 5491; Abu Seif, Salah
- The Last Kiss, القبله الاخيره, 5492; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 1, القبله الاخيره, 5493; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 2, القبله الاخيره, 5494; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 3, القبله الاخيره, 5495; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 4, القبله الاخيره, 5496
  - The Last Kiss Still 5, القبله الاخيره, 5497; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 6, القبله الاخيره, 5498; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 7, القبله الاخيره, 5499; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 8, القبله الاخيره, 5500; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 9, القبله الاخيره, 5501; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 10, القبله الاخيره, 5502; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 11, القبله الاخيره, 5503; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 12, القبله الاخيره, 5504; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 13, القبله الاخيره, 5505; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 14, القبله الاخيره, 5506; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 15, القبله الاخيره, 5507; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 16, القبله الاخيره, 5508; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 17, القبله الاخيره, 5509; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 18, القبله الاخيره, 5510; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 19, القبله الاخيره, 5511; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 20, القبله الاخيره, 5512; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 21, القبله الاخيره, 5513; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - The Last Kiss Still 22, القبله الاخيره, 5514; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
- Awake and Relaxed, فايق ورايق, 5515; Rafla, Helmy
  - Awake and Relaxed Still 1, فايق ورايق, 5516; Rafla, Helmy
  - Awake and Relaxed Still 2, فايق ورايق, 5517; Rafla, Helmy
  - Awake and Relaxed Still 3, فايق ورايق, 5518; Rafla, Helmy
- The Operation (Operation 77), العمليه, 5519; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 1, العمليه, 5520; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 2, العمليه, 5521; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 3, العمليه, 5522; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 4, العمليه, 5523; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 5, العمليه, 5524; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 6, العمليه, 5525; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 7, العمليه, 5526; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 8, العمليه, 5527; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 9, العمليه, 5528; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 10, العمليه, 5529; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 11, العمليه, 5530; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 12, العمليه, 5531; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 13, العمليه, 5532; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 14, العمليه, 5533; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 15, العمليه, 5534; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 16, العمليه, 5535; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 17, العمليه, 5536; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 18, العمليه, 5537; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 19, العمليه, 5538; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 20, العمليه, 5539; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Operation Still 21, العمليه, 5540; Mostafa, Niazi
- His Majesty, صاحب الجلاله, 5541; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 1, صاحب الجلاله, 5542; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 2, صاحب الجلاله, 5543; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 3, صاحب الجلاله, 5544; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 4, صاحب الجلاله, 5545; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 5, صاحب الجلاله, 5546; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 6, صاحب الجلاله, 5547; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 7, صاحب الجلاله, 5548; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 8, صاحب الجلاله, 5549; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 9, صاحب الجلاله, 5550; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 10, صاحب الجلاله, 5551; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 11, صاحب الجلاله, 5552; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 12, صاحب الجلاله, 5553; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 13, صاحب الجلاله, 5554; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 14, صاحب الجلاله, 5555; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 15, صاحب الجلاله, 5556; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 16, صاحب الجلاله, 5557; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - His Majesty Still 17, صاحب الجلاله, 5558; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
- My Wife's Demon/Goblin, عفريت مراتي, 5559; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 1, عفريت مراتي, 5560; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 2, عفريت مراتي, 5561; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 3, عفريت مراتي, 5562; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 4, عفريت مراتي, 5563; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 5, عفريت مراتي, 5564; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 6, عفريت مراتي, 5565; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 7, عفريت مراتي, 5566; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 8, عفريت مراتي, 5567; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 9, عفريت مراتي, 5568; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 10, عفريت مراتي, 5569; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 11, عفريت مراتي, 5570; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 12, عفريت مراتي, 5571; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
  - My Wife's Demon/Goblin Still 13, عفريت مراتي, 5572; Abdel Wahab, Fateen
- The Glass Threshold, العتبه جزاز, 5573; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 1, العتبه جزاز, 5574; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 2, العتبه جزاز, 5575; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 3, العتبه جزاز, 5576; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 4, العتبه جزاز, 5577; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 5, العتبه جزاز, 5578; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 6, العتبه جزاز, 5579; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 7, العتبه جزاز, 5580; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 8, العتبه جزاز, 5581; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 9, العتبه جزاز, 5582; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 10, العتبه جزاز, 5583; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 11, العتبه جزاز, 5584; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 12, العتبه جزاز, 5585; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 13, العتبه جزاز, 5586; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 14, العتبه جزاز, 5587; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 15, العتبه جزاز, 5588; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 16, العتبه جزاز, 5589; Mostafa, Niazi
  - The Glass Threshold Still 17, العتبه جزاز, 5590; Mostafa, Niazi
- For Men Only, للرجال فقط, 5591; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 1, للرجال فقط, 5592; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 2, للرجال فقط, 5593; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 3., للرجال فقط, 5594; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 4, للرجال فقط, 5595; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 5, للرجال فقط, 5596; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 6, للرجال فقط, 5597; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 7, للرجال فقط, 5598; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 8, للرجال فقط, 5599; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 9, للرجال فقط, 5600; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 10, للرجال فقط, 5601; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 11, للرجال فقط, 5602; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 12, للرجال فقط, 5603; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 13, للرجال فقط, 5604; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 14, للرجال فقط, 5605; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - For Men Only Still 15, للرجال فقط, 5606; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
- Love in August, غرام في اغسطس, 5607; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 1, غرام في اغسطس, 5608; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 2, غرام في اغسطس, 5609; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 3, غرام في اغسطس, 5610; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 4, غرام في اغسطس, 5611; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 5, غرام في اغسطس, 5612; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 6, غرام في اغسطس, 5613; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 7, غرام في اغسطس, 5614; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 8, غرام في اغسطس, 5615; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 9, غرام في اغسطس, 5616; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 10, غرام في اغسطس, 5617; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 11, غرام في اغسطس, 5618; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 12, غرام في اغسطس, 5619; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 13, غرام في اغسطس, 5620; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 14, غرام في اغسطس, 5621; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 15, غرام في اغسطس, 5622; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 16, غرام في اغسطس, 5623; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 17, غرام في اغسطس, 5624; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 18, غرام في اغسطس, 5625; Saifi, Hassan
  - Love in August Still 19, غرام في اغسطس, 5626; Saifi, Hassan
- If I Were A Man, لو كنت رجلا, 5675; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 1, لو كنت رجلا, 5676; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 2, لو كنت رجلا, 5677; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 3, لو كنت رجلا, 5678; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 4, لو كنت رجلا, 5679; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 5, لو كنت رجلا, 5680; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 6, لو كنت رجلا, 5681; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 7, لو كنت رجلا, 5682; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 8, لو كنت رجلا, 5683; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 9, لو كنت رجلا, 5684; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 10, لو كنت رجلا, 5685; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 11, لو كنت رجلا, 5686; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 12, لو كنت رجلا, 5687; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 13, لو كنت رجلا, 5688; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 14, لو كنت رجلا, 5689; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 15, لو كنت رجلا, 5690; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 16, لو كنت رجلا, 5691; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 17, لو كنت رجلا, 5692; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 18, لو كنت رجلا, 5693; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 19, لو كنت رجلا, 5694; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 20, لو كنت رجلا, 5695; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 21, لو كنت رجلا, 5696; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 22, لو كنت رجلا, 5697; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 23, لو كنت رجلا, 5698; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 24, لو كنت رجلا, 5699; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 25, لو كنت رجلا, 5700; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
  - If I Were A Man Still 26, لو كنت رجلا, 5701; Diaa Dine, Ahmed
- Don't Think Of Me, لا تفكرين, 5627; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 1, لا تفكرين, 5628; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 2, لا تفكرين, 5629; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 3, لا تفكرين, 5630; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 4, لا تفكرين, 5631; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 5, لا تفكرين, 5632; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 6, لا تفكرين, 5633; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 7, لا تفكرين, 5634; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 8, لا تفكرين, 5635; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 9, لا تفكرين, 5636; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 10, لا تفكرين, 5637; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 11, لا تفكرين, 5638; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 12, لا تفكرين, 5639; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 13, لا تفكرين, 5640; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 14, لا تفكرين, 5641; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 15, لا تفكرين, 5642; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 16, لا تفكرين, 5643; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 17, لا تفكرين, 5644; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 18, لا تفكرين, 5645; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 19, لا تفكرين, 5646; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 20, لا تفكرين, 5647; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 21, لا تفكرين, 5648; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 22, لا تفكرين, 5649; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 23, لا تفكرين, 5650; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 24, لا تفكرين, 5651; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 25, لا تفكرين, 5652; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 26, لا تفكرين, 5653; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 27, لا تفكرين, 5654; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 28, لا تفكرين, 5655; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 29, لا تفكرين, 5656; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 30, لا تفكرين, 5666; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 31, لا تفكرين, 5667; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 32, لا تفكرين, 5668; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 33, لا تفكرين, 5669; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 34, لا تفكرين, 5670; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 35, لا تفكرين, 5671; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 36, لا تفكرين, 5672; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 37, لا تفكرين, 5673; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
  - Don't Think Of Me Still 38, لا تفكرين, 5674; Zulfiquar, Mahmoud
- Anger, الغضب, 5702; Anwar Shinawi
  - Anger Still 1, الغضب, 5703; Anwar Shinawi
  - Anger Still 2, الغضب, 5704; Anwar Shinawi
  - Anger Still 3, الغضب, 5705; Anwar Shinawi
  - Anger Still 4, الغضب, 5706; Anwar Shinawi
- Every House Has a Man, 1949; ref107
  - Every House Has a Man | Actors in Image: Faten Hamama, 1949; ref107_000001; Rafla, Helmy; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Pianos; Women; Negative Images; Films; Actors; Costumes; Lanterns/Lamps; Telephones; Clocks/Watches
  - Every House Has a Man | Actors in Image: Amina Rizk, Mahmoud El Meleigy, Faten Hamama, 1949; ref107_000002; Barakat, Henry; 1 negatives; 94 x 119 cm (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Women; Films; Negative Images; Men; Costumes; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Lanterns/Lamps; Furnishings; Actors
  - Every House Has a Man | Actors in Image: Mahmoud El Meleigy, Faten Hamama, 1949; ref107_000003; Barakat, Henry; 1 negatives; 94 x 145 cm (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Women; Jewelry; Negative Images; Clocks/Watches; Men; Films; Actors; Costumes; Furnishings